<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<events>
  <item>
    <title>AGM Milano 2014</title>
    <summary>The Anual General Meeting of ESN!</summary>
    <date>
      <start>+1 day</start>
      <start>+4 days</start>
    </date>
    <body><![CDATA[><h3>About</h3><p>All the ESN sections in Milan (ESN Milano Statale, ESN Politecnico Milano, ESN Iulm Milano, ESN Bocconi Milano, ESN Milano Bicocca and ESN Unicatt) are ready to make their own dream come true: hosting the Annual General Meeting 2014!</p><h3>Mission</h3><p>Our dream is to provide the guests the &quot;best AGM in the World&quot;&hellip;<br />...in a beautiful Italian city easy to reach&hellip;<br />...providing quick transfers between accommodation and plenaries&hellip;.<br />...organizing crazy parties&hellip;<br />...tasting fine food...<br />...and much more!<br /><br />Follow us to discover upcoming news and further details about our programme.&nbsp;</p><h3>Description</h3><p>The Annual General Meeting (AGM) is the highest decision-making body of Erasmus Student Network taking place every year; all the Sections of the Network participate in it with more than 600 people.</p><h3>General information</h3><p>After their candidacy in 2012, Milano and its 6 great ESN Sections are ready to host the Annual General Meeting 2014!!!<br /><br />All the ESN sections of the city collaborate in order to provide their Erasmus and Exchange students the best activities and events that all the people from different universities can enjoy.<br /><br />Their ability to handle with big numbers of people and their previous experiences in organizing International and National events (National Platforms, National Events, a South Western European Platform and a Council of National Delegates), makes them skilled to plan an event with no place for setbacks or hitchs.<br /><br />The support of institutional and commercial partners collaborating with them on several projects, makes them also capable to provide exclusive locations and first rate services, as well as cultural and professional additional events.<br /><br />Last but not least, they all strongly believe in the project born for the candidacy of AGM 2013 and in the team supporting it.</p>
    <!]]></body>
    <image>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/milano2.jpg</image>
    <spotlight>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/milano.jpg</spotlight>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>NBM Athens</title>
    <summary>The National Boards' Meeting (NBM) is a bi-annual ESN event, where members of different National Boards come together.</summary>
    <date>
      <start>2014-05-15</start>
      <end>2014-05-18</end>
    </date>
    <body><![CDATA[><p>Dear participant,</p>

<p>Here you can register for the NBM Athens 2014. Participation fee is 50 euro and it includes 3 nights at the Hostel (Thursday to Saturday), breakfast, warm meals and transportation for the three days of the NBM (Friday to Sunday) and free entrance to all the night activities of this event (no drinks included).</p>

<p>Please remember that you should pay as soon as you are accepted by the OC, not earlier, and no later than 10 days after the end of the registration. Your final registration is confirmed as soon as we received your payment.</p>

<p>(Final Payment Deadline: 25 April 2014)</p>

<p>The OC of NBM Athens 2014</p>

<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/NBM-Athens-2014/247237102118920?ref=ts&amp;fref=ts" target="_blank">NBM FACEBOOK PAGE</a><br><a href="mailto:nbmathens.oc@gmail.com?subject=NBM%20Athens">NBM OC EMAIL</a></p>
    <!]]></body>
    <image>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.png</image>
    <spotlight>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.spotlight.png</spotlight>
    <gallery>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.1.png</gallery>
    <gallery>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.2.png</gallery>
    <gallery>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.3.jpg</gallery>
    <gallery>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.4.jpg</gallery>
    <gallery>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.5.jpg</gallery>
    <gallery>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.6.jpg</gallery>
    <gallery>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.7.jpg</gallery>
    <gallery>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.8.jpg</gallery>
    <gallery>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NBM_Athens.9.jpg</gallery>
  </item>

</events>