<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<partners>
  <item>
    <title>IT committee</title>
    <body><![CDATA[>
    The IT committee is very awesome! they made my awesome website!
    <!]]></body>
    <logo>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/ESN_astronaut.png</logo>
    <link>
      <title>Facebook page</title>
      <url>https://www.facebook.com/ESN.IT.Committee</url>
    </link>
    <link>
      <title>Page on esn.org</title>
      <url>http://www.esn.org/committees/it</url>
    </link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>New Yorker</title>
    <body><![CDATA[>
    <p>New Yorker and the International Erasmus Exchange Student Network have one thing in common: the young people who are the focus of their activities – you!&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a partner to the network, we assist with projects aimed at providing you with knowledge and skills within an international company. In the future, there are plans to offer student projects and social events that you can take part in.</p>
<p>The partnership has begun with the introduction of an exclusive New Yorker Discount Card, which gives you, as members of the network, a one-off discount of 20% on your purchase in any of our stores.</p>
<p>We are an international fashion company with over 960 branches in 38 countries. Our stores offer trendy young fashion, denim, sportswear and streetwear, as well as accessories and underwear. Our product range includes our own brands Amisu, Smog, Fishbone and Censored, with the collections changing to suit the latest international fashion trends every season. You can find more information on our clothing and company on our official website <a href="http://www.newyorker.eu/">www.newyorker.eu</a>.</p><!]]></body>
    <logo>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/NY_Logos.png</logo>
    <link>
      <title>New Yorker</title>
      <url>http://www.newyorker.eu/</url>
    </link>
    <link>
      <title>Facebook page</title>
      <url>https://www.facebook.com/NewYorker.Fashion</url>
    </link>
    <link>
      <title>Page on esn.org</title>
      <url>http://esn.org/partner/new-yorker</url>
    </link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Housing Anywhere</title>
    <body><![CDATA[>
    <p>Students who go on exchange or internship and want to rent out their room can use our housing platform on <a href="http://www.HousingAnywhere.com">www.HousingAnywhere.com</a>. You can earn some extra money for your exchange by renting out your room, and you will help our university with increasing the supply of short-stay housing for the incoming exchange students.</p><!]]></body>
    <logo>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/HousingAnywhere.png</logo>
    <link>
      <title>Housing Anywhere</title>
      <url>http://www.housinganywhere.com/</url>
    </link>
    <link>
      <title>Facebook page</title>
      <url>https://www.facebook.com/HousingAnywherecom</url>
    </link>
    <link>
      <title>Page on esn.org</title>
      <url>http://esn.org/partner/housing-anywhere</url>
    </link>
  </item>
  <item>
      <title>Eurail.Com</title>
      <body><![CDATA[>
      <h3>Who are we?</h3>
<p>Eurail.com&nbsp;is the online store for your European rail passes. Eurail.com is a fast growing e-commerce company which sells&nbsp;<a href="http://esncard.org/discount/eurailcom" target="_blank">Eurail</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="http://esncard.org/discount/interraileu" target="_blank">InterRail</a>&nbsp;train passes online, and provides first-class customer service and expert travel advice. Our rail passes let you visit up to 30 European countries by train.</p>
<h3>Do I need a Eurail or an InterRail pass?</h3>
<p>Non-European ESN students who want to explore Europe by train can order their passes at <a href="http://esncard.org/discount/eurailcom" target="_blank">www.eurail.com</a>.</p>
<p>European ESN students and non-European ESN students who have been in Europe for at least 6 months can order their InterRail pass at&nbsp;<a href="http://esncard.org/discount/interraileu" target="_blank">www.interrail.eu</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p>We understand this might be a bit confusing. So if you’re not quite sure whether you can travel with a Eurail or InterRail pass, just&nbsp;<a href="http://www.eurail.com/help/choosing-pass/should-i-travel-eurail-or-interrail?utm_source=ESN&amp;utm_medium=SITE&amp;utm_campaign=ESNEM">take our little test.</a></p>
<h3>ESN &amp; Eurail.com</h3>
<p>As an ESN student you’re staying at a new place and making friends from all over the world. We can imagine that during or after your study abroad you want to explore more places in Europe than just the country you study in. And what better way for you and your friends to explore Europe than with the freedom of a rail pass. &nbsp;Travel Europe with a Eurail or InterRail pass and get the train journey of a lifetime!</p>
<h3>Let’s get in touch!</h3>
<p>Are you already daydreaming about all the places you want to visit? “Like” our award-winning <a href="http://www.facebook.com/eurorail" target="_blank">Facebook</a> page and follow us on <a href="http://www.twitter.com/eurail" target="_blank">Twitter</a> to read our top travel tips and to connect with like-minded travelers from all over, plus find out about our latest offers! Want extra travel inspiration? Check out our boards on <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/eurail" target="_blank">Pinterest</a>!</p>
<p>Contact our Customer Service Team via Facebook or Twitter, or email us for advice on choosing the right InterRail pass and help planning your trip: <a href="mailto:esn@eurail.com">esn@eurail.com</a>.&nbsp;</p><!]]></body>
      <logo>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/Eurail.png</logo>
      <link>
        <title>Eurail.Com</title>
        <url>http://www.eurail.com/</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <title>Facebook page</title>
        <url>https://www.facebook.com/eurail</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <title>Page on esn.org</title>
        <url>http://esn.org/partner/eurailcom</url>
      </link>
    </item>
  </partners>